Kála Leslie

kala.leslie@gmail.com / (971)-263-6123

SUMMARY

A reliable, hard working, dedicated team player with over 15 years experience in Information Technology who is a quick learner with a desire for continued personal growth. Background in customer service, project management, documentation, system administration, and hardware support.

SKILLS

Windows 7/8/10 DHCP Backup Software
Windows Server 2008/2016/2019 DNS Video Conferencing

Active Directory/Azure PowerShell Anti-virus
Exchange 2008/2016 VMware Networking
Office 2010/2016/365 Ticketing Systems Printers

EXPERIENCE

Systems Engineer, InterDent Service Corporation – Vancouver, WA

2015 - 2018

Promoted from Systems Analyst II

- Administer virtual and physical servers; including support and maintenance
- Lead client engineering process; configure all deployment tools
- Manage Active Directory, group policy, and DHCP
- Provide Tier 1-3 remote and on-site technical support and IT education/training in over 200 physical locations
- Configure and maintain ticketing system, automations, knowledge base, and process documents

Desktop Analyst, PeaceHealth SW Medical Center - Vancouver, WA

2014 - 2015

- Configure and troubleshoot network servers and network ports
- Manage Active Directory user security
- Lead and participate in software deployment projects
- Coordinate vendor equipment repair and upgrades

Operations Engineer, DECK Monitoring – Portland, OR

2012 - 2014

- Generate quotes for products, services, fulfill client orders, and update apps with logistical information
- Configure, pack, and ship equipment; verify comms and network once equipment is installed
- Create and alter web pages, analyze client data, track issues, report application bugs and feature requests
- Create knowledge-base, process documents, and AutoCAD diagrams for individual client network topology

Junior Field Engineer, U.S. Technical Services – Huntington Beach, CA

2008 - 2011

Promoted from TOC Help Desk (Tactical Operations Closet)

- Manage and document backups and backup tape retention policies
- Proactive maintenance and monitoring of critical client systems in a 24/7 call-center environment
- Create support documents for both customers' knowledge-base, as well as internal wiki
- Support internal and office staff with technical issues

EDUCATION

AA Fine Arts & Humanities, Saddleback Community College – Mission Viejo, CA